Lothar Wolff collection, 1926-1987
George Eastman Museum
- Series 2, Film/TV Projects, 1932-1986
  - Subseries 17,The TV Bible, 1980-1985; undated
    - no title (Box C304)
      - [TV Bible“Episode 1: Abraham – The Beginning” Script -- Second Draft], 1987 (Folder 12)
        With rewrites and marginalia. Dated 11/2/1983.
      - ["1. Folge: Abraham Teil 1" and Exodus Treatments], ca. 1980 (Folder 13)
        [TV Bible"Episode 1: Abraham Part 1"] and Exodus story treatments. Undated, in German.
      - "The Television Bible: The Old Testament as a TV Series", 1982 (Folder 14)
        Comb-bound promotional book from Taurus Film. Includes undated clipping.
      - "The Television Bible: The Old Testament as a TV Series -- 'Joseph, The Book of Genesis'", 1982 (Folder 15)
        Comb-bound promotional book from Taurus Film. Two copies.
      - "The Television Bible: The Old Testament as a TV Series -- 'Moses, The Book of Exodus,'", 1982 (Folder 16)
        Comb-bound promotional book from Taurus Film.
      - Bible Taurus Film G.m.b.H. correspondence, 1976; 1980-1984 (Folder 17)
        Correspondence with Heinrich Krauss,Wolf Maknowitz,Allan Sloane,Marianne Rohrmoser,Nils Nilson,Georges Klotz regarding TV Bible; invoices; contracts; receipts; clippings regarding the Bible; applications for tax exemption certificates;The Old Testament as a TV Series project proposal; production schedule graph; map of Jersusalem; photocopies of 1976 German magazine article and a legal document, both involving German TV broadcaster ZDF. In German, English.
      - Bible Project Documents, 1980 (Folder 18)
        Correspondence with Nils Nilson,Allan Sloane,Heinrich Krauss;New York Times article regarding sales of the Bible; "Anhang: Abraham als 'Begründer des Monotheismus' [Appendix: Abraham as 'Founder of Monotheism']." In German and English.
      - TV Bible Proposal Drafts and Supplement, ca. 1982 (Folder 19)
        Series proposal drafts and supplemental "Synopsis of the 'Old Testament' Narrative Elements." Comments and marginalia in English and German.
      - [Binder labeled "TV Bible Script Drafts Part II"], 1983-1984 (Folder 20)
        Script and treatment drafts with comments, photocopies of Bible passages. In English and German.
      - [Unlabeled binder, "TV Bible'Episode 2: Abraham Part Two Script'"], 1981; 1984 (Folder 21)
        Script by Allan Sloane, with cover letter from Wolff dated 8/29/1984; 4/9/1971 Time magazine clipping regarding made-for-TV Biblical epics.
      - "Bible" Clippings, 1980-1984 (Folder 22)
        Newspaper and magazine clippings about the Bible, Biblical adaptations, and theology. In English and German.
      - "The Bible" Notes & News Magazine Articles, 1980-1981 (Folder 23)
        April 1981 Saturday Evening Post article about filming the Bible; notes, comments regarding a "What Is the Bible?" introductory film and episode treatments. In English and German.
      - New York Times clipping "Paraphrase of the Bible a Big Seller,", 1985 (Folder 24)
        Photocopy of 2/28/1985 article about bestselling Bible adaptation The Book.
      - Bible/Egypt Prod., 1983 (Folder 25)
        Correspondence regarding production manager Ahmed Sami.
      - TV Bible Notes, 1980-1983 (Folder 26)
        Notes, correspondence. In English and German.
      - Critique of "Abraham" Script, 1983 (Folder 27)
        Allan Sloane's critique of John Bowen's TV Bible script, related correspondence.
      - Taurus Expenses, Payments, 1983-1984 (Folder 28)
        Receipts (including card receipt with number), invoice, expense report, bills, related correspondence.
      - Expenses Bible Munich, 1981-1982 (Folder 29)
        Expense reports, receipts, bills. Additional expenses notations on folder in Wolff's hand. In German and English.
      - Receipts, Etc., 1982 (Folder 30)
        Airline/train tickets and receipts, discount cards with color photo of Wolff, bank receipts, hotel receipts, several credit card receipts with account number visible, invoice. Music recital program; political flyer and sticker. In Italian, German, and English.
      - Taurus Film/Expenses, 1980-1982 (Folder 31)
        Airline/train tickets and receipts, phone bills, expense report for Fernsehbibel/[TV Bible] project, related correspondence. In English, French and German.
    - no title (Box C354)
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie], ca. 1980 (Folder 1)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series] Comb-bound booklet. Series proposal. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie"Gliederung und Inhalte"], 1981 (Folder 2)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series"Structure and Content"] Comb-bound booklet dated 2/12/1981. Overview of series structure and 32 proposed episodes. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie"Treatment 27 & 28: König Salomo"], 1982 (Folder 3)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series"Treatments 27 & 28: King Solomon"] Comb-bound booklet dated 10/31/1982. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie"Leitlinien für die Drehbuchentwicklung"], ca. 1980 (Folder 4)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series"Guidelines for Script Development"] Undated comb-bound booklet. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie], ca. 1980 (Folder 5)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series] Undated comb-bound booklet. Expanded 221-page series overview with description of series objective and method; three screenplay sketches; structure and content overview; appendix. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie"Folgen 1-7: Buch Genesis Einführung und Synopse"], 1980 (Folder 6)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series"Episodes 1-7: Genesis Introduction and Synopsis"] Comb-bound booklet dated 10/15/1980, subtitled "The Filming of the Book of Genesis." Introductory material, overview of episodes 1 through 7. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "1. Folge: Abraham Teil I" & "2. Folge: Abraham Teil II" Screenplays], 1980; 1982 (Folder 7)
        ["Episode 1: Abraham Part I" & "Episode 2: Abraham Part II"] Binder containing introductory TV Bible material and episode screenplays. "Abraham Part I" is marked "3rd revise" and dated 1/28/1982. In German with English notations and marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "3. Folge: Der Segen Isaaks" & "4. Folge: Jakobs Frauen"] Screenplays, 1980; 1982 (Folder 7a)
        ["Episode 3: The Blessing of Isaac" & "Episode 4: Jacob's Wives"] Binder containing TV Bible screenplays. In German with English notations and marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "Karol Sidon Abraham (1. Teil)"], 1984 (Folder 8)
        ["Abraham (Part 1)"]TV Bible screenplay dated February 9, 1984. In German.
      - [Unlabeled Folder, "Abraham 1. Folge (Gen 12 -16)" Draft], 1980 (Folder 9)
        ["Abraham Episode 1 (Gen 12-16)]TV Bible draft dated 4/7/1980. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: "Folgen 1-7: Zur Verfilmung des Buches Genesis -- Die Eigenart der biblischen Vorlage" Screenplay], 1980 (Folder 10)
        [TV Bible: "Episodes 1-7: For the Film Adaptation of the Book of Genesis: The Nature of the Biblical Template"] Screenplay dated August 15, 1980. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "2. Folge: Abraham Teil II" Treatment], ca. 1980 (Folder 11)
        ["Episode 2: Abraham Part II"] Undated TV Bible treatment. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "2. Folge: Abraham Teil II" Draft], 1980 (Folder 12)
        ["Episode 2: Abraham Part II"]TV Bible draft dated 7/20/1980. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "3. Folge: Der Segen Isaaks" Rough Draft], 1980 (Folder 13)
        ["Episode 3: The Blessing of Isaac"]TV Bible rough draft dated 7/25/1980, marked "Old Version" and "New one 15.Sept.80" in Wolff's hand. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "3. Folge: Der Segen Isaaks" Draft], 1980 (Folder 14)
        ["Episode 3: The Blessing of Isaac"]TV Bible draft dated 11/11/1980. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "4. Folge: Jakobs Frauen" Draft with Changes], 1980 (Folder 15)
        ["Episode 3: Jacob's Wives"]TV Bible draft dated 9/15/1980 with changes dated 11/14/1980. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "4. Folge: Jakobs Frauen" Rough Draft], 1980 (Folder 16)
        ["Episode 4: Jacob's Wives"]TV Bible rough draft dated 8/6/1980 and marked "outdated version." In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "5. Folge: Jakob und Seine Söhne" and "Patriarchengeschichten: Folge 5 und 6" Drafts], 1980 (Folder 17)
        ["Episode 5: Jacob and His Sons"]TV Bible draft dated 11/15/1980 and ["Stories of the Patriarchs: Episode 5 and 6"], draft dated 7/7/1980. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Untitled folder, "6. Folge: Josef in Ägypten" Draft], 1980 (Folder 18)
        ["Episode 6: Joseph in Egypt"]TV Bible draft dated 7/22/1980. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Untitled folder, "7. Folge: Die Versöhnung der Brüder" Draft], 1980 (Folder 19)
        ["Episode 7: The Reconciliation of the Brothers"]TV Bible draft dated 7/23/1980. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Untitled folder,Fernsehbibel"8. Folge: Der Brennende Dornbusch" Draft], 1981 (Folder 20)
        [Television Bible"Episode 8: The Burning Bush"] Draft dated 4/30/1981, with attached note from Heinrich Krauss. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Untitled,Fernsehbibel"9. Folge: Exodus" Treatment Draft], 1981 (Folder 21)
        [Television Bible"Episode 9: Exodus"] Treatment draft dated April 8, 1981. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Untitled, "10. Folge: Sinai" Draft], 1981 (Folder 22)
        ["Episode 10: Sinai"]TV Bible draft dated 4/30/1981. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Untitled folder,Fernsehbibel"11. Folge: Das Goldene Kalb (= Mose IV)" Treatment Drafts], 1981 (Folder 23)
        [Television Bible"Episode 11: The Golden Calf (= Moses IV)"] Two treatment drafts dated 6/1/1981 and 6/29/1981. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel"12. Folge: Joshuas Zug Über Den Jordan" Treatment Drafts], 1981 (Folder 24)
        [Television Bible"Episode 12: Joshua's Train Over the Jordan"] Treatment drafts dated 5/26, 6/2, and 6/28/1981.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "13. Folge -- Die Richter" and "Die Richter, I. Teil: Ehud -- Debora" Treatments], 1982 (Folder 25)
        ["Episode 13: Judges"] Undated TV Bible treatment marked "Outdated" and "Split 13 into 2 parts 5/14/82"; ["Episode 13: Judges, Part I: Ehud -- Debora"], treatment dated 5/15/1982. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "13. Folge: Die Bücher Josua und Richter" Background], ca. 1982 (Folder 26)
        ["Episode 13: The Books of Joshua and Judges"] Undated TV Bible background material. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "Folge 13a Die Richter II: Gideon -- Abimelech -- Jiftach" Treatment], 1982 (Folder 27)
        ["Episode 13a Judges II: Gideon -- Abimelech -- Jepthah"]TV Bible treatment. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel"Folge 13b: Rut" Treatment Draft], 1982 (Folder 28)
        [Television Bible"Episode 13b: Ruth"] Treatment draft dated 6/22/1982. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel"14. Folge: Samuel und Saul, I. Teil: Simson -- Samuel" Treatment], 1982 (Folder 29)
        [Television Bible"Episode 14: Samuel and Saul, Part I: Samson -- Samuel"] Treatment dated 5/26/1982. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "Mose", Outline and Notes], ca. 1982 (Folder 30)
        ["Moses"]TV Bible material. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder, "Die Patriarchengeschichten" Outline and Notes], ca. 1982 (Folder 31)
        ["The Patriarch Stories"]TV Bible material. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel"Folge 14a: Samuel und Saul, II. Teil: Sauls Erwählung" Treatment], 1982 (Folder 32)
        ["Television Bible Episode 14a: Samuel and Saul, Part II: Saul's Election"] Treatment dated 6/4/1982. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel"Folge 14b: Samuel und Saul, III. Teil: Sauls Verwerfung" Draft], 1982 (Folder 33)
        ["Television Bible Episode 14b: Samuel and Saul, Part III: Saul's Rejection"] Draft dated 6/7/1982. In German with English marginalia.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie"Folgen 13-18: Von Joshua Bis Saul, Einführung und Synopse"], 1982 (Folder 34)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series"Episodes 13-18: From Joshua to Saul, Introduction and Synopsis"] Comb-bound booklet dated September 1, 1982. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie"Treatment 17 & 18: König Saul"], 1982 (Folder 35)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series"Treatments 17 & 18: King Saul"] Comb-bound booklet contains treatments dated 8/17/1982 .Heinrich Krauss business card. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie"Treatment 13-16: Die Zeit der Richter"], 1982 (Folder 36)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series"Treatments 13-16: The Period of the Judges"] Comb-bound booklet containing treatments of Episode 13, dated 3/31/1982; Episode 14, dated 7/31/1982; Episode 15, dated 8/7/1982; and Episode 16, dated 8/8/1982. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie"Treatment 23-26: Davids Thronnachfolge"], 1982 (Folder 37)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series"Treatments 23-26: David's Succession"] Comb-bound booklet dated 10/23/1982. Three copies. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie"Folgen 19-28: David und Salomo, Einführung und Synopse"], 1982 (Folder 38)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series"Episodes 19-28: David and Solomon, Introduction and Synopsis"] Comb-bound booklet dated 11/15/1982. In German.
      - [Unlabeled folder,Fernsehbibel: Das Alte Testament als TV-Serie"Treatment 19-22: Davids Aufstieg"], 1982 (Folder 39)
        [Television Bible: The Old Testament as TV-Series"Treatments 19-22: David's Rise"] Comb-bound booklet dated 10/15/1982. In German.
  - Subseries 18,Wild, Wild World of Animals, 1973-1975
    - no title (Box C314)
      - Other People, Other Places -- Screenings in Hamburg, Germany to Buy Films, 1973-1975 (Folder 11)
        Outlines of documentary shorts available from Polytel International Film-und-Fernseh GmbH; screening reports; correspondence regarding German TV series about Antarctica [in English and German]; newspaper clippings; outline of "Mad Zoo/Neurotic Zoo" film project [in French].
      - Other People, Other Places-- Ratings and Publicity, Some with Wild, Wild World of Animals, 1973-1975 (Folder 16)
        Correspondence regarding ratings, viewer response; Nielsen ratings charts; syndication reports;Variety"Prime-Access Reviews."
      - Other People, Other Places -- Misc. Correspondence, 1971; 1973-1975 (Folder 18)
        Correspondence and drafts regarding licensing agreements, employee vacation time, disposition of files, writers' fees for Wild, Wild World of Animals.
      - Wild, Wild World of Animals, 1973 (Folder 27)
      - Wild, Wild World of Animals-- Ratings, 1973-1974 (Folder 28)
        Newspaper clippings; full-page Variety ad;Wild, Wild World of Animals ratings reports; distribution list.
      - WWWOA Viewer Letters Wild, Wild World of Animals, 1973-1974 (Folder 29)
        Correspondence; one letter regarding Other People, Other Places.
  - Subseries 19,Windjammer: The Voyage of the Christian Radich, 1957-1958
    - no title (Box C300)
      - [Album labeled "Puerto Rico Fortaleza, Feb. 57"], 1957-1958 (Folder 3)
        Photographs and negatives shot at La Fortaleza, Puerto Rico, during the production of Windjammer. Subjects include Wolff,Louis de Rochemont,Pablo Casals,Mieczyslaw Horszowski,Governor Luis Muñoz Marín,Arthur Fiedler.
    - no title (Box C368)
      - [Newspaper Clippings, 1951-1966] (Folder 16)
  - Subseries 20,The World We Live In, 1968-1974; 1981-1986; undated
    - Sub-subseries 1,General, 1968-1974; undated
      - no title (Box C019)
        - [CINE 1971 certificate for "How Old Is Old?"/Life Around Us] (Folder 4)
          Certificate congratulating Time-Life Films.
      - no title (Box C314)
        - Articles on The World We Live In& Correspondence & Statistics, 1968-1972 (Folder 21)
          Promotional folder; full-page magazine ads;Time-Life Films press releases; segment synopses; newspaper television listings pages; newspaper reviews; series broadcast calendar; Public Broadcasting Service weekly programming reports;Pem’s Personal Buddies entertainment newsletter.
        - The World We Live In-- Financial, 1969-1970 (Folder 22)
          Monthly financial status accounts.
        - Life Around Us-- Announcements, Articles etc. Statistics,], 1970-1974 (Folder 23)
          Correspondence;MoMA press releases and program notes; full-page New York Times ad for Time-Life Films; segment synopses and credits;Time-Life Films Lunch-Hour Film Festival flier;New York Times"The Guide" Sunday insert 3/1/1981; episode ratings [in German] with attached letter [in English]; rating reports from local US stations; newspaper TV listing; selected press clips.
        - Life Around Us-- Press Kit, undated (Folder 24)
          Series press kit, including 35mm transparencies, 8 x 10 black-and-white photographs, live announce copy transcript, promotional brochure (using the title The World We Live In, two paper printing matrices, segment synopses and credits.
        - Time/Life Journal Copy, Oct. 17, 1969 (Folder 34)
      - no title (Box C367)
        - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1930-1960; 1971-1972; ca. 1983; undated (Folder 14)
          Black-and-white photograph of Wolff receiving a CINE 1969 award for the "Survival in the Sea" episode of The World We Live In.
      - no title (Box OS-1)
        - [The 13 Clocks, earth and moon artwork;Life Around Us], ca. 1960; ca. 1970; undated (Folder 5)
          Large promotional brochure for Life Around Us TV series.
    - Sub-subseries 2, "The Not-So-Solid Earth,", 1971-1972; undated
      - [8th Annual Landers Associates Award of Merit to The Not-So-Solid Earth], ca. 1972
        Certificate with gold seal.
      - no title (Box C019A)
        - [American Film Festival Blue Ribbon Award for "The Not-So-Solid Earth"], 1972
          Award certificate
      - no title (Box C352B)
        - [American Film Festival Blue Ribbon Award for "The Not-So-Solid Earth"], 1972
    - Sub-subseries 3, "Rock-a-Bye Baby,", 1971-1972; 1981-1986
      - no title (Box C014)
        - Blue Ribbon Award for "Rock-a-Bye Baby" for Education Film Library Association of the American Film Festival, 1972 (Folder 25)
      - no title (Box C019A)
        - [Two American Film Festival Blue Ribbon Awards for "Rock-a-Bye Baby"], 1972
          Two framed certificates.
      - no title (Box C301)
        - Biobehavioral Systems --Jim Prescott, 1981-1986 (Folder 8)
          Correspondence, series prospectus, clippings and other research materials, newsletter regarding "Rock-a-Bye Baby," "The Roots of Violence," and child development.
      - no title (Box C314)
        - Articles on "Rock-a-bye Baby,", 1971-1972 (Folder 26)
          F.Y.I.,Time, Inc. newsletter; 1972 American Film Festival winners review;Time-Life Films promotional material and press release; correspondence regarding American Film Festival, Edinburgh Festival, Cine Awards; newspaper clippings regarding Cine Awards, American Film Festival; reviews.
      - no title (Box C356)
        - [American Film Festival Blue Ribbon Award for "Rock-A-Bye Baby"], 1972
  - Subseries 21, Miscellaneous, ca. 1932; 1938; 1948-1967; 1973-1986; undated
    - no title (Box C301)
      - George Stingl,Aradt-Film, 1981-1982 (Folder 2)
        Correspondence regarding film Adolph Hitler -- A Career, book Children of the Holocaust; 20-page treatment for TV production featuring Sylvia Ulrich[in German].
      - Helen Brew(Filmmaker)The One Child Family,China in Change and PR Material for These Programs, 1984-1985 (Folder 10)
        Correspondence regarding The One Child Family film and its adaptation for a TV series about early child development; newspaper clippings about child development, infant mortality, child abuse; press notes; Christmas card; proposed "Foundations of Life" project.
      - Stewart Halperin, 1980-1982 (Folder 22)
        Correspondence with US photographer Stewart Halperin and Swiss artist Theo Meier, primarily regarding a "Theo Meier project"; magazine article about Meier; "Proposed locations for filming"; slide sheet of 12 35mm transparencies taken by Halperin featuring Meier in his Thailand studio; 9/1980 Adventure Travel magazine article [photocopy] "Thailand: Trekking the Golden Triangle" by Halperin.
      - Robert Conte,HBO Manager, 1983 (Folder 24)
        Correspondence regarding Vera Wolff’s Rescue, a projected film about the 1943 rescue of 7,000 Danish Jews from the Nazis;Crying Time script about the after-effects of Agent Orange.
      - IBM--Sterling Norris, 1984 (Folder 29)
        Correspondence concerning "The Glory of Bach," aka "The Wonder of Bach," project.
      - Independent Film GmbH München"Project Bali,", 1975 (Folder 31)
        Three-page synopsis of "Projekt Bali" from Independent Film GmbH.
      - Nicole Jouve(Interama), 1977-81 (Folder 32)
        Correspondence and materials regarding various film projects, including:The Joy of Bach,The Mediterranean, "Then and Now,"Martial Arts in Japan, an "anthropological series,"Look at the World, and others.
      - Lazi Film-- Exposé by Karl-Werner Kobialka, undated (Folder 41)
        Synopsis of Rauhreif uber Baden-Baden[photocopy, in German].
      - Lazi Film--Heinz v. Matthey, 1982 (Folder 43)
        Correspondence [in German] from producer Heinz von Matthey regarding ecology films, filming bovine embryo-transfer.
      - Lazi Film--Heinz v. Matthey to William J. Kirby, 1982 (Folder 44)
        Correspondence between producer Heinz von Matthey and William J. Kirby, vice-chairman, counsel and secretary, of the John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, regarding possible WDR/Lazi Films series "Ecology."
      - Lazi Film-- Lothar Wolff, 1982-1983 (Folder 45)
        Correspondence regarding "the Ecology project"; a possible sequel series to Planet Earth.
      - Lazi Film-- Lothar Wolff to William J. Kirby, MacArthur Foundation, 1982 (Folder 46)
        Correspondence with William J. Kirby, vice-chairman, counsel and secretary, of the John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, regarding a television series on global ecology.
      - Michael Lopen, 1984 (Folder 47)
        Correspondence regarding a film project about the rescue of Danish Jews from Nazis; proposal for a film about an escape from Romanian POW camp during WWII.
      - Theo Meier, 1983 (Folder 49)
        Correspondence concerning Swiss artist Theo Meier; magazine article [photocopy] "The Art of Living: Chiang Mai’s Theo Meier"; abstract of book The Painter Theo Meier: Pictures from the Tropics by Klaus Wenk.
      - Polygon Productions, Sussex England, "Animals and Men" Project, 1976 (Folder 61)
        Letter from Stanley Joseph/Polygon Productions regarding "Animals and Men" project, synopses attached.
      - Quest Productions, 1977 (Folder 66)
        Correspondence; cancelled check [photocopy]; line-item production budget; production schedule; memo regarding "Winter Soldiers" production.